Wakey wakey tunes. It's that time of
year again.
You're letting us out
only because I'm contractually obligated
to since it's Halloween.
>> Thank you, Sandicus.
Truly, you have our gratitude.
>> Yeah. Yeah. You know the rules. Just be
back before the end of October. Yay.
[Music]
You stay in that cage. It's their time
to be out of my basement, not yours.
Eat your oatmeal. I spiced it up with
some holiday sprinkles, some baby
carrots, and some cilantro. So, don't
say I never do anything for you. and
stop trying to win me over by looking in
my eyes. Empathy is a foreign concept to
me.
Astro, come help me with a goddamn lawn
mower.
It's not working. Did you remember to
prime it?
>> Oh no, I forgot to do that. Well, well,
well. Look who's using a push mower.
Don't even got one of those big
expensive ones that you sit on. What do
you think? My legs wouldn't even reach
the pedals. Oh, yeah. I forgot you're so
short. No, you don't. You remind me
every goddamn day.
Turn the lawn mower off, you tweet. I
can't. It's out of my control.
What are you doing? I'm turning on the
other lawn mower. How is that supposed
to help me?
I'm thinking that if we're lucky,
they'll run into each other like bumper
cars. Or maybe it will start chasing me
too, you dork.
>> You're going to unal alive me. Well,
maybe you deserve to be unal alive for
being the biggest bully in the whole
stinking neighborhood.
>> Dandy, that's a horrible thing to say.
>> You are mean.
[Applause]
Um, Sprout, you okay there, baby girl?
[Music]
>> Yep. Sprout Seedley is dead.
>> Damn. Who could have ever guessed with
his body parts laying all over the
place? You are so perspective, Roger.
>> Thank you. Oh, this Halloween is going
to be a disaster. Instead of enjoying
the festivities this year, we're going
to be mourning the death of one of our
dearest friends. Speak for yourself. I
saw Sprout lugging in a whole shipment
of full-sized candy bars he was going to
hand out to trick-or-treaters. I'm going
to break into his house and steal it.
Now that he can't tell me no and hand it
out myself so I can be the talk of the
neighborhood. What happened?
Sprout, speak to me. What did they do to
you? I tried to stop him. He just took a
shotgun and well, I told him not to do
it. But you know how it is. [__] always
does his own thing. Sprout chose to end
things on his own terms and we have to
respect that.
>> Dandy, that's not
>> Why is the underside of the lawn mower
covered in blood?
>> Why don't you mind your own business,
[__] You're lying. Someone is lying.
Sprout would have never done that
without me. Cuz we have a pact that we'd
do it together when the time was right.
Well, doesn't that just sound like the
gayest [__]
>> You remember our promise under the
starllet sky, right, Sprout? That we'd
always be together.
Just so you know, when I unal alive
myself, you're going to do it, too. You
got that? Cuz nobody is going to tap
that ass but me. You got that? What? No,
I'm not doing that. You're crazy. That's
bananas.
Sprout. Sprout. Sprout.
>> Damn. His head really is just one big
strawberry. We should make a pie.
>> You unalived him. You unalived Sprout.
You unalived my boyfriend. I I mean my
best friend.
You want to be run over, too, Twink.
>> Sandy, calm down. You're losing yourself
to your own madness.
>> Who's next? Who else wants to step up on
Dandekus? Nobody. I didn't think so. No.
It won't end like this. Sprout told me
what to do should a day like this ever
come to pass. We can revive him.
>> How?
>> [__] shut up and he will tell us.
>> Cosmo, we know you want him back, but
Sprout is already down in hell. We are
tunes. Do you really think we would be
allowed through the fires of hell or the
gates of heaven? We are not beings
created by God.
>> How can you be so sure,
>> [__] Tisha exists. If God has a plan,
it wouldn't involve a living tissue box.
If we can gather up Sprout's body parts,
we can just put him back together.
>> Well, I'd better be off so I can get
ready to hand out candy to the child
tunes. If I wait too long, I'll have so
much candy left over and it will go
right to my butt.
>> Damn, he's carrying the weight of those
butt cheeks. It's no wonder why he has
the slowest speed in the whole game.
I want to lick those stinky armpit
leaves until they're sping wet. Someone
would have to drag me away by force.
>> Astro, stop getting distracted.
>> Oh, sorry.
>> We need to keep digging until we find
enough body parts to replace the missing
ones.
[Music]
Hey, Astro, give me your towel.
>> You mean my anxiety blanket?
>> I worked up a huge sweat digging up
those body parts.
>> Yeah, breathe it in, you dog. You like
that boy stink, don't you?
[Music]
>> Is that glisten? How is he gliding?
Oh no, he's just riding an electric
scooter. Damn, I always wanted one of
those. I wonder how much they cost. Keep
digging, dork. Sprout, look everybody at
Sprout. They can't see me, you dweeb.
I'm haunting you specifically because
you piss me off. How have you returned?
What do you think? I showed up at the
gates of heaven and God sent me
downstairs because I'm gay. But Satan
didn't want me either because while he
was reading my list of sins to see which
of the seven levels I would spend
eternity on, I told him to shut up
because he was being annoying. So, I'm
stuck here on this mortal plane. What
are you doing? Cosmo said, "If we can
find enough body parts to replace your
old ones, we can bring you back to
life." Okay, bring the body parts into
my house. Don't drop him coming up the
stairs.
[Music]
Okay, here's what we're going to do.
Dandy. Sticking out of that tub of ice
cream on the table is an aluminum ice
cream scooper. That metal rod is
connected to V through jumper cables.
And then there are more jumper cables
connecting V to Sprout's succulent
nipples. Dandy, you're going to have to
fart on the rod. The vibrations will
pass straight into V, which should cause
her to short circuit because she's a TV
and [__] That electricity will then
pass into Sprout, jolting him back to
life. Astro, you need to install the
Door Dash app on your phone and order me
a brown sugar boba tea. Shelly, you go
in the kitchen and do my dishes. Does
everyone understand what I'm saying?
>> No,
>> not really. Well, we're doing it anyway.
Dandy, I hope you've been holding in a
fat one. You should go into your new
husk. Don't tell me what to do.
[Music]
We need more farting power. Don't have
to ask me twice, [__]
>> You can do it, Dandy. Block that ass.
>> Nobody asked for your input, Shelly.
Just keep doing those dishes.
It's working. It's working.
Dandy, you unal alived me. I'm going to
get you.
>> Dandy, you told us he blew his brains
out with a shotgun.
>> This dweeb ran over me with a lawn
mower.
>> Dandy, why did you do it?
>> You don't ask questions. I can do what I
want. It's my world. You're all just
living in it. Now, everybody start
cutting. We got to go reberry the body
parts.
I have a delivery of one boba tea for
Mr. Astronovalite. Goob, what's with the
vest? It's a bulletproof vest. The
Halloween tunes are planning a revolt
against all of Gardens's view. They have
already taken over Little Caesars and
have taken Finn and Shrimpo as hostages.
The tunes haven't been able to eat for 4
hours. At this point, they are all going
to starve to death, which is why I took
this Door Dash job. So, I do what I can
to help be delivering food. Damn it. I
knew I shouldn't have released those
Halloweenies. They've been out to get me
from day one. All because I keep them
locked up in my basement 334 days of the
year.
>> Look, it's Gordy. Hi, Gordy.
>> Holy [__]
>> Get inside, Goo.
>> I'll be fine. I have a bulletproof vest,
remember?
No. Cosmos Boba Tea.
>> Get back here, you little twerp. Huddle
up, tunes. I've got a plan.
He is still not dead. How is such a
thing possible?
>> I'm a shrimp, dumbass. I can literally
breathe underwater.
>> I'm shrimp old [__] I will speak
however I want. You don't know our pain.
You don't know what it's like living
every day of the year in a deep, dark
dungeon, eating nothing but oatmeal,
only to be let out one month out of the
year.
>> Cool. I don't give a [__]
>> What is the outcome of your quest, sexy
baby? Is Sir Dandicus dead?
>> No, I accidentally shot Goop instead
because he was standing in my line of
fire.
>> Well, how many times did you shoot? Just
once.
>> [__] we told you guns have six bullets
in them. You couldn't have tried at
least a couple more times.
>> Oh my god, [__] Will you shut up? I am
only like 3 years old. You expect me to
know how guns work? I literally just
learned what a gun is 5 minutes ago. Oh
my god, [__] Shut up. My parents are
dead.
>> Do not yell at the sexy baby Rebecca. He
is not yet at the age where he can be
aware that he is challenged mentally.
Hey girlies. Sprout.
>> Mr. Seedley.
>> Sup kiddo. I mean actually I'm not
Sprout, but I'll take it as a compliment
because Sprout is sexy. I'm another
Halloween tune like you guys. My name is
Spit.
>> The jester lies.
>> No, I'm being dead ass.
>> Prove it then, sir Spit.
>> If I was Sprout, could I do this?
The homosexual speaks true.
>> I moved to Gardens View while y'all were
locked in Dandy's basement, which is why
we're only able to meet now. Word around
Gardens View is you [__] are also
planning a revolt. Count me in. But if
we're going to take over more than just
Little Caesars, we're going to need a
ton more weapons. Cuz your gay little
kitchen knife isn't going to cut it. You
know who has the most weapons in town?
Dandy. Let's go into his basement and
steal his guns. Uh, that sounds stupid.
We left his basement for a reason. We're
not going back. I don't even recall ever
seeing any weapons in there.
>> You shall open your mouth no further,
Wench. If we are, you vanquish the evil
that is Dandy's world. We need an
arsenal of top caliber. Take us to
Dandy's basement, oh fruity one.
What sort of betrayal has fallen upon
us?
>> [__] I told you that was sprout, but
nobody ever listens to me because y'all
are stupid.
>> Close your speakhole, sexy baby, and get
ready to fight.
>> They may be event tunes, but we can take
them. We're mains at the end of the day.
[Music]
>> So, you wish to fight me oneon-one? Very
well. It shall be a duel then. We shall
duel then with nightly honor only with
blades.
>> Who's your daddy? Who's your daddy?
>> Danny, here's the box my electric
scooter came in. We can use it to trap
the Halloween too.
[Music]
Dandy, you need to poke holes in the box
so they can get air.
>> That's what you sound like. [__] shut
up. I know what I'm doing.
[Music]
What are you doing, Sylvester? We're
trying to save you.
>> We would rather suffocate within the
confines of this box than live the rest
of our days under you.
>> Yeah, we don't want to go back. Dandy,
you didn't tell us you kept them held
hostage like this all year long.
>> I told you I kept them locked in my
basement. What did you think was down
here? A Nintendo Switch?
>> Dandy, all tunes deserve to live free.
You're a flower you should know better
than anybody. How would you feel if you
were like stuck in a pot since you're
like a flower?
>> Uh, fine. It was getting to be too many
mouse to feed anyway.
I guess you can all have houses in the
neighborhood. On one condition, you all
rarely come outside.
[Applause]
[Music]
>> It took a bit of time to gather up all
your body parts. You're lucky you've got
me around to piece you back together.
Nobody else cared. Guess I owe you my
life then, huh?
[Music]
Well, [__] Maybe I should thank you
properly, [__]
Start cleaning the place up, Dweeb.
We're so glad you're alive, Sprout.
Hey guys, I'm still alive because I was
wearing a bulletproof vest.
Be careful with him. I just put him back
together.
[Music]
Nothing some of your superhealing baked
cookies won't fix. What do you say we
head to the kitchen and test out how
stable this body of mine really is?
Smell you later, dorks.
I thought the kitchen was on the other
side of the house.
[Laughter]
Go Roger. Go Roger. Go Roger. Go Roger.
Go.
[Music]
My
mother.
[Music]
in my knowledge
about
[Music]
Got to do
something.
3.
Hey
[Music]
my [__] my
son. Who the [__] my son?
I got my
baby.
[Music]
Heat. Heat.